Guide to the Richard Kelly Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Project files, 1939-1977; Series I
  - Motel on the Mountain (See also: Mount Hillburn Corporation), 1955
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 45)
  - Mount Hillburn Corporation (See also: Motel on the Mountain), 1955
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 45)
    - Drawings (Box 45, Box 386)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 45)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 45, Box 386)
  - Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute (See Also: Utica Museum), 1960
    Job location: Utica, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 84, Box 405)
    - Drawings (Box 84, Box 229)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 84)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 84)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 84, Box 229)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 84, Box 229)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 84, Box 229)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 84)
    - Photographs (Box 84)
  - Murphy, Patrica Apartment, 1950
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 45)
    - Drawings (Box 45)
  - Patricia Murphy Candlelight Restaurant, 1954
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 45, Box 404)
    - Drawings (Box 45)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 45)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 45)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 45)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 45)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 45)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 45)
    - Photographs (Box 45)
  - Patricia Murphy Candlelight Restaurant, 1953
    Job location: Westchester, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 45)
    - Drawings (Box 45)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 45)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 45)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 45)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 45)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 45)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 45)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 45)
    - Photographs (Box 45)
  - Museum of Contemporary Crafts, 1955
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 45)
    - Drawings (Box 45)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 45)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 45)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 45)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 46)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 46)
    - Photographs (Box 46, Box 405)
  - Museum of Modern Art (Ain House), 1950
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 46)
  - Museum of Modern Art (Garden), 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 46)
    - Drawings (Box 46, Box 253, Box 289)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 253)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 253)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 46, Box 289)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 46)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 46, Box 289)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 46, Box 253)
    - Photographs (Box 46)
  - Museum of Modern Art (New Building Addition), 1963
    - Drawings (Box 289)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 289)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 289)
  - Museum of Modern Art (Penthouse), 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 46)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 405)
  - Museum of Modern Art (Union News Restaurant), 1953
    Job location: New York, ny
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 405)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 405)
  - Music Center, 1961
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 46)
    - Drawings (Box 46)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 46)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 46)
    - Photographs (Box 46)
  - Mystic Museum
    Job location: Mystic, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 46)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 46)
  - National Cathode Corporation
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 47)
    - Drawings (Box 47)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 47)
  - National Geographic Building, 1963
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 47)
    - Drawings (Box 47)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 47)
  - National Museum of Jerusalem, 1965
    Job location: Jerusalem, Israel
    - Unidentified Material (Box 360)
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 360)
    - Drawings (Box 360)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 360)
  - National Naval Medical Center, 1963
    Job location: Bethesda, MD
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 47)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 47)
  - A. Neri Corporation
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 47)
    - Drawings (Box 47)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 47)
  - New Gallery, 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 47)
  - New Harmony Church, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 47)
    - Drawings (Box 47)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 47)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 47)
  - New Harmony Shrine, 1959
    Job location: New Harmony, IN
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 47)
  - New Jersey State Capitol Development Program, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 47)
    - Drawings (Box 119, Box 287, Box 324)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 119)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 119, Box 287, Box 324)
    - Photographs (Box 47)
  - New York City Center of Music, Dance, and Drama, 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 48)
    - Drawings (Box 48, Box 405)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 48, Box 405)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 48)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 48)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 48)
  - New York Coliseum, 1955
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 49)
    - Drawings (Box 49)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 49)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 49)
  - New York Design, Inc., Exhibition Room, 1948
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 49)
    - Drawings (Box 49)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 49)
  - New York Hilton
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 49)
    - Drawings (Box 244)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 244)
    - Photographs (Box 49)
  - New York International Idlewild Airport, 1957
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 49)
    - Drawings (Box 49)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 49)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 49)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 49, Box 386)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 49)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 49)
    - Photographs (Box 49)
  - New York International Idlewild Airport, British Overseas Airways Corporation, 1957
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 49)
    - Drawings (Box 49)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 49)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 49)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 49)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 49)
  - New York Produce Exchange, 1958
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 50)
    - Drawings (Box 50)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 50)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 50)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 50)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 50)
  - New York University, Institute of Fine Arts, 1969
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 50)
    - Drawings (Box 50)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 50)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 50)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 50)
  - New York University, James Duke House, 1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 50)
    - Drawings (Box 50)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 50)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 50)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 50)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 50)
    - Photographs (Box 50)
  - New York World's Fair, 1939-1940
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 50, Box 405, Box 412)
    - Drawings (Box 50, Box 186–187, Box 368)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 405)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 50, Box 186–187, Box 405)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 50, Box 186–187, Box 368)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 187)
    - Photographs (Box 405)
    - Material Samples (Box 405)
  - New York World's Fair, Parker Pen Pavilion, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 50)
    - Photographs (Box 50)
  - Marie Nichols, Inc., 1955
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 50)
    - Drawings (Box 50)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 50)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 50)
  - Norfolk Street Lighting
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 51, Box 405)
    - Drawings (Box 389)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 51)
  - North Carolina Art Museum and Archives (aka: North Carolina Museum of Art), 1950
    Job location: Raleigh, NC
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 51)
    - Drawings (Box 51)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 51)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 51)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 51)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 51)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 51)
  - North Carolina National Bank
    Job location: Charlotte, NC
    - Unidentified Material (Box 360)
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 360)
    - Drawings (Box 360)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 360)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 42)
  - Northern Trust Company, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 51–55, Box 405)
    - Drawings (Box 51–55, Box 180, Box 185, Box 241, Box 249–250, Box 278, Box 305, Box 319, Box 327, Box 332–334, Box 380)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 51–55, Box 319)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 51–55, Box 241, Box 319, Box 326, Box 332–333)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 51–55, Box 185, Box 241, Box 305, Box 332–334, Box 380, Box 399)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 51–55, Box 180, Box 185, Box 241, Box 249–250, Box 278, Box 305, Box 334)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 51–55, Box 185, Box 334)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 55)
    - Photographs (Box 55)
  - Norton Simon Museum of Art, 1976
    Job location: Pasadena, CA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 55)
    - Drawings (Box 55)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 55)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 55)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 55, Box 401)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 55, Box 401)
  - Novak Apartment, 1963
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 55)
    - Drawings (Box 55, Box 320)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 55)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 55)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 55)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 55)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 55, Box 320)
    - Photographs (Box 55)
  - Noyes, Eliot Residence
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 55)
    - Drawings (Box 55)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 55)
    - Photographs (Box 55)
  - N.Y.N.H. & Hartford Railroad, 1955
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 55)
    - Drawings (Box 55)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 55)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 55)
  - Oakland Metropolitan International Terminal
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 56)
  - O'Hare Guest House
    - Drawings (Box 159)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 159)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 159)
  - O'Hare International Airport, 1962
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 56)
    - Drawings (Box 56, Box 123, Box 274, Box 336)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 56)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 56, Box 123, Box 336)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 56, Box 123, Box 274, Box 336)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 56, Box 123, Box 336)
  - Ohio State Capitol (See Also: State House)
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 79)
  - Ohio State University, 1962
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 56)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 56)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 56)
    - Photographs (Box 56)
  - Ohrbach's Inc.
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 56)
    - Drawings (Box 56, Box 166)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 56)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 56)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 56, Box 166)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 56, Box 166)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 166)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 166)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 166)
  - Old Age and Survivors Insurance Building
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 57)
    - Drawings (Box 57)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 57)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 57)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 57)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 57)
  - Oneto House, 1952
    Job location: Irvington, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 57)
    - Drawings (Box 57)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 57)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 57)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 57)
    - Photographs (Box 57)
  - Orkin Residence
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 57)
    - Drawings (Box 57)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 57)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 57)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 57)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 57)
  - Orpheum Theater
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 399)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 399)
  - Oslo Embassy
    Job location: Oslo, Norway
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 57)
    - Drawings (Box 57)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 57)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 57)
    - Photographs (Box 32)
  - Otterbourg, Steindler, Houston, & Rosen
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 405)
  - Pace-Setter House
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 412)
  - Pack, Howard Residence, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 57)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 57)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 57)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 57)
  - Pahlman, William, 1947
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 58)
    - Drawings (Box 58)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 58)
  - Paley Plaza, 1966
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 58)
    - Drawings (Box 58)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 58)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 58)
  - Pardee, Irving, 1947
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 58)
    - Drawings (Box 58)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 58)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 58)
  - Park Avenue South, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 58)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 58)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 58)
  - Park Lane Hotel, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 58)
    - Drawings (Box 58, Box 258)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 58)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 58)
  - Paul Mellon Center for British Art, Yale University, 1974
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 58–59, Box 346, Box 406)
    - Drawings (Box 58–59, Box 95–96, Box 100–101, Box 103–104, Box 107, Box 109–110, Box 115–118, Box 346)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 58–59, Box 110, Box 346, Box 400, Box 406)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 58–59, Box 391, Box 400)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 58–59, Box 101, Box 104, Box 115–117, Box 400, Box 406)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 58–59, Box 95–96, Box 100, Box 103, Box 107, Box 109, Box 115–118, Box 406)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 58–59, Box 95–96, Box 104, Box 392–393, Box 406)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 95–96, Box 103)
    - Material Samples (Box 346)
  - Pavilion Lodge
    Job location: Avalon, Catalina, CA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 59)
    - Drawings (Box 59)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 59)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 59)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 59)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 59)
  - Peachtree Baker Hotel, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 60)
    - Drawings (Box 262)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 60)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 262)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 262)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 262)
  - Peck + Peck, 1948
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 60)
    - Drawings (Box 60)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 60)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 60)
  - Pennsylvania Drug Company, 1950-1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 60)
    - Drawings (Box 60)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 60)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 60)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 60)
    - Drawings (Box 60)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 60)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 60)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 60, Box 386)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 60)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 60, Box 386)
  - Pennsylvania State College, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 61)
    - Drawings (Box 61)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 61)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 61)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 60–61, Box 386)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 60–61, Box 386)
  - Pennsylvania State Office Building, 1950-1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 61)
    - Drawings (Box 61)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 61, Box 387)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 387)
  - Pennsylvania Transportation Center, 1956
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 61)
    - Drawings (Box 61)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 61)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 61)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 61)
    - Photographs (Box 61)
  - Pepis, Apartment for Miss Betty, 1959
    - Drawings (Box 155)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 155)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 155)
  - Peratt, Valentine Residence, 1958
    Job location: Cleveland, OH
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 61)
    - Drawings (Box 61)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 61)
  - Petroleum Club, Exxon Mobil Building (See Also: Humble Oil and Refining Company), 1963
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 28, Box 61–62)
    - Drawings (Box 28, Box 132, Box 199)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 28, Box 132)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 28, Box 132, Box 199)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 28, Box 132, Box 199)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 28, Box 132)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 28, Box 132)
    - Photographs (Box 28)
  - Petroleum Club, 1954
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 62)
    - Drawings (Box 61–62, Box 134)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 62)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 62)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 61–62, Box 134)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 61–62, Box 134)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 61–62, Box 134)
  - Philadelphia Academy of Music, 1956
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 62–63, Box 387)
    - Drawings (Box 63)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 63)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 63)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 62–63, Box 387)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 63)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 62–63, Box 387)
  - Philadelphia City Hall Courtyard, 1958
    - Drawings (Box 158)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 158)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 158)
  - Philadelphia City Planning Exhibition, 1947
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 63, Box 406)
    - Drawings (Box 63)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 63)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 63)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 63)
    - Photographs (Box 63)
  - Philadelphia National Bank
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 63)
    - Drawings (Box 63)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 63)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 63)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 63)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 63)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 63)
  - Philadelphia Office Building, 1956
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 182)
    - Drawings (Box 182)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 182)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 182)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 182)
  - Philadelphia Redevelopment
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 63)
    - Drawings (Box 63)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 63)
  - Philadephia Panorama, Permanent Exhibition
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 63)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 63)
    - Photographs (Box 63)
  - Philadelphia State Office Building, 1958
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 63)
    - Drawings (Box 63)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 63)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 63)
  - Phillips Petroleum Company, Pier 66 Motor Hotel, 1964
    Job location: Fort Lauderdale, FL
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 64)
    - Drawings (Box 64, Box 154, Box 161, Box 197, Box 268, Box 284)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 64, Box 154, Box 161, Box 197)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 64)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 64, Box 154, Box 161, Box 197)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 64, Box 161, Box 268, Box 284)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 64, Box 161, Box 284)
  - Phoenix Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 64)
    - Drawings (Box 64, Box 198, Box 210, Box 262)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 64)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 64, Box 262)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 64, Box 198, Box 210)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 64, Box 198, Box 210)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 64, Box 198, Box 210)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 64)
  - Place Ville Marie (See Also: Royal Bank of Canada), 1963
    Job location: Montreal, Quebec, Canada
    Collaborator: I.M.Pei & Associates
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 65)
    - Drawings (Box 65, Box 164, Box 168, Box 176, Box 188, Box 376)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 65, Box 164)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 164)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 65, Box 168, Box 176, Box 376)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 65, Box 164, Box 168, Box 176, Box 376)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 65, Box 164, Box 168, Box 176)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 168, Box 176)
  - Planetarium, 1965
    Job location: Calgary, Canada
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 65)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 65)
  - Plaza de Panama
    - Drawings (Box 131)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 131)
  - Plaza Tower, 1969
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 65)
    - Drawings (Box 65)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 65)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 65)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 65)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 65)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 65)
    - Photographs (Box 65)
  - Polkowitz Residence, 1961
    Job location: South Orange, NJ
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 65)
    - Drawings (Box 65)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 65)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 65)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 65)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 65)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 65)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 65)
  - Pontchartrain Hotel, 1963
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 66, Box 406)
    - Drawings (Box 66, Box 126, Box 154, Box 213, Box 227, Box 406)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 66, Box 126, Box 154, Box 195, Box 213, Box 227)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 66, Box 154, Box 195, Box 213, Box 227)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 66, Box 126, Box 154, Box 195, Box 406)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 66, Box 126)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 66, Box 126)
  - Post War House, 1950-1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 66)
    - Drawings (Box 66)